

ROMAN KHOMETS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT)

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Hi, I'm a quality focused front-end developer with experience in creating SPA using React/Redux/Rest API stack. Pay extreme attention to detail and have a passion for delivering a great user experience. Also, provide strong critical analysis and problem solving. Currently focusing to enhance knowledge of Node.js, Express and React Native

CONTACTS



Petrikov, Belarus



+375 33 675 53 96









SKILLS

React Redux (Redux Toolkit) **Typescript** Node.is Rest API (Axios) Formik Jest Git SASS, Responsive Layout Material UI

LANGUAGES

Ant Design

Photoshop

English (A2+/B1) Russian/Belarusian (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - current

Freelance

- · Implemented and typed data access layer to poor-documented API
- Created React module components
- · Added screening and debouncing to search input field 2019 - current

Individual Entrepreneur (Construction Service)

- Developed and implemented strategic business plan in a highly competitive market environment
- Fostering relationships to maintain existing clients, while developing new relationships to attract potential clients
- Designed and implemented marketing campaigns, resulting in ~30% orders increase
- Encourages employees to do their best and increased work productivity immensely 2017 - 2019

Installation Crew Chief

- Managed 3 person team of installers
- Guide efforts to improve technological process in a real and cost effective way, resulting in saving of the worktime for about a half of an hour per day
- Trained new employees

EDUCATION

2021 - current

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics Engineer of Information Technology and Control

2021 - current

IT-Incubator

Frontend Developer

2017 - 2021

Bobruisk State College of Forestry

Forestry Technician

ACTIVITIES

DIY amateur Car travelling Care of homeless animals